

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hernan-calvo-937a64199/

GITHUB

https://github.com/HernanCalvoFullStack

PORTFOLIO

https://portfoliohernancalvo.netlify.app

I'm a programming student, I have strong training in Mathematics and Full Satck MERN Web Development. I have excellent analysis, planning and teamwork skills that I acquired in the various positions in which I worked during my career.

PERSONAL DATA

FECHA DE NAC. 07.08.1984

DNI 30.050.257

Olivos, Buenos Aires

CONTACT

Phone Number: 116-212-7899

E-Mail

calvohernan1984@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

Spanish (Native) Enlish C2

CALVO HERNÁN ALEJANDRO

Full Stack Web Developer - MERN

SKILLS: HTML5 - CSS (SASS Y TAILWINDCSS) - JAVASCRIPT - REACT JS - TYPESCRIPT - NODE JS (EXPRESS)

EDUCATION

21st Century University

2023 – in Progress

Bachelor in Data Science (18/54 subjects)

Institute Joaquín V. González

Mathematics Teachers (Debt 5 finals)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Deputy Director of Technical Support - Presidency of the Nation

January 2024 – July 2024

Accounting analyst - José J. Chediack

December 2021 - December 2023

Administrative - Ministry of Economy - Presidency of the Nation

April 2021 - December 2023

Administrative - Legal and Technical Secretariat – GCABA

December 2019 - April 2021.

Director of Administrative Management - SLYT - Presidency of the Nation

September 2017 - December 2019

Head of Office - SLYT - Presidency of the Nation

March 2016 – September 2017

Administrative - Ministry of Production - Presidency of the Nation

March 2016 - March 2017

Administrative Operational Management Official Gazette - GCABA

June 2007 - February 2016

COURSES

UDEMY

<u>2021 – Desarrollo Web Completo con HTML5, CSS3, JS AJAX PHP y</u> MySQL

2022 – JavaScript Moderno Guía Definitiva

<u>2022 – React y TypeScript - La Guía Completa: Hooks Context</u> <u>Redux MERN</u>

<u>2023 – Node.js – Bootcamp Desarrollo Web inc. MVC y REST APIs</u>